trainers4me.com 2019-10-13

# Privacy Policy - Trainers4Me

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy statement describes how Trainers4me collects and uses the personal information you provide us with on our website trainers4me.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

1 **. COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify you ("personal information"), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses, user name and password. We collect the following personal information from you if you choose to become a Member and register with us: 

  * Contact Information such as name, e-mail address or phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit or debit card number and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number or password

In addition, as is true of most websites, even if you do not register or become a Member we automatically gather information from your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. This information does not include personally identifiable information about you.

We use this information to:

  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Improve our website and marketing efforts
  * Send you confirmation for sign up
  * Send you newsletters
  * Respond to your questions

2 **. COOKIES**

We may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file, which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to:  

  * Estimate our audience size and usage pattern
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customise our website according to your individual interests
  * Speed up your searches
  * Recognise you when you return to our website

3.  **GENERAL OPERATIONAL PURPOSES  
**  
We may use information gathered from you for various purposes in order to:

  * Ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer
  * Share information about our Trainers, their lessons and other details about lesson reservations
  * Notify you about changes to our services
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of our services when you choose to do so
  * Conduct statistical analysis
  * Develop and improve our website

4\. **SOCIAL NETWORK ACCOUNTS  
**  
You can log into our website using social network accounts, including Facebook and Google+. This service will authenticate your identity and provide you with the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name, e-mail address and photo to pre-populate your profile.

5\. **STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA  
**  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA and working for us or one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your booking, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By consenting to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

6\. **EDITING AND DELETING DATA  
**  
Every user of our website, either Members or Trainers, can regulate and modify their personal information (name, phone number etc.) in their profile without requiring our permission. However, if the Member or Trainer wishes to delete their Trainers4me account they must send us an e-mail regarding their cancellation to: support@trainers4me. Cancelling an account is free of charge.

7\. **E-MAILING VIA A TRAINERS4ME ACCOUNT  
**  
The Members’ Trainers4me e-mail addresses must only be used for the purpose of sending the e-mail communication to the addressee. If you, as a Member, want to unsubscribe from receiving e-mails, you can do so through the ‘E-mail Notifications’ section in your profile. 

8\. **SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**  
Our website uses a secure processing server (https://) when collecting information (both personal and concerned with payment). 

9\. **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, we will notify our Members and Trainers about them by e-mail. 

10\. **CONTACT INFORMATION  
**  
If you require more information about our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us at: support@trainers4me.com.
